[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 6]
[Pearl Pavilion]
Damn fish demon,
come here, come here, come here.
How is Master?
He is very quiet.
Except sleeping,
he spends most of the time playing in the Code
and rarely comes out.
Okay.
Please keep an eye on him for me.
If anything happens,
just let me know.
Thank you.
Lu Li.
Didn't Liu Shao
mention when to let me
go back?
Are you in such a hurry to go back?
Even if you are
at the risk of being discovered.
Miss Liu Shao said that
I was her demon.
You are her demon?
I'm her man.
What's wrong?
Is he...
I mean
the man protecting her.
You must not know that
I received 30,000 taels of silver from her.
I must be responsible for everything about her.
Everything?
I mean,
I need to let her live safely
in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Who's responsible for the missing King Herb?
You are responsible for it.
Your master, Demon King in White, is responsible for it.
Bai Feng,
the night patrol disciples
who are responsible for the northwest woods are not back yet.
You two keep patrolling.
I'll take a look.
I remember you.
Lu Li is your junior.
Ao Hen,
kill me if you want.
Cut the crap.
What matters is that I don't want to kill you.
I want to cooperate with you.
I recover my strength by absorbing spirit.
You can help me.
As Marquis Wuyang's disciple,
how can I cooperate with a demon like you?
Don't worry.
To show my sincerity,
I'll give you a big gift first.
There's an Aquatic Demon
in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
So what?
Aquatic Demons are elites.
We can't arrest them as we want.
Let me give you another suggestion.
When you arrest him,
don't let him get any water.
When it's done,
you can come to me again.
I am leaving, little girl.
Little girl,
you have a lot of discontents.
But since you're so weak,
you can't get
what you want.
Soul-Devouring Spell works like this.
Is there any solution?
Why does it work again?
If you fall in love with Liu Shao,
Soul-Devouring Spell will be triggered.
It will make your blood vessels expand oppositely and cause you pain.
No.
I have to find a way to suppress the Soul-Devouring Spell.
When the spell returns to your palm,
you will die.
If that's the case,
I can only avoid meeting Liu Shao.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
One day,
two days,
three days.
Liu Shao.
Why are you sitting here for so long?
Four days.
I'm counting the days
when I haven't seen Lu Li
after leaving Pearl Pavilion,
I wonder
what he's doing now.
Boss,
you asked me to let Liu Shao and the demon meet more.
Do you want them to be together?
I always think that you and Liu Shao
are the most suitable couple.
Are you alright?
Stop talking nonsense.
Liu Shao and I are...
We are just...
There is only employment between us.
That's all.
Boss, who are you lying to?
You're double-faced.
Anyway,
I have my own ideas.
You figure this out.
Don't let Liu Shao approach me again.
Yes, boss.
I understand what you mean.
You just don't want Liu Shao to bother you.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
I will get it done.
Why is Lu Li avoiding meeting me lately?
Tell me.
Will you die if you tell me the truth?
Why do you like to punch me in the chest
like my boss?
You...
Will you tell me the truth?
Will you?
I...
Listen,
I will never
betray my boss.
You're quite loyal.
Xue,
why don't you give the cake you made
to Senior Xu
and Senior Wan?
They love it too.
After all,
Senior Xu is handsome
and Senior Wan is good at sword fighting.
They are both better than this fatty.
No, no, no.
Okay.
Go.
Xue...
Xue.
Do you want to say it?
I'll tell you, okay?
The Soul-Devouring Spell is getting worse.
It's not a good idea
to keep hiding from Liu Shao.
Lu Li.
Senior,
you...
what's up?
You don't look well.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
I am just
tired from practicing.
I'm fine.
By the way,
I found this
on the window of the wall nearby.
I hope
that person is you.
Will you be that person?
Senior,
I gave this sound-leaving stone to Liu Shao.
Why did you take it away?
Liu Shao?
I thought it was for me.
Can't I touch it?
This concerns Liu Shao...
Do you know...
Do you like Liu Shao that much?
I thought there shouldn't be so many concerns
in our relationship.
Lu Li,
Your spiritual power and hers are born to be opposing.
You are destined not to be together.
If you insist,
if Master finds it out,
he won't let Liu Shao go.
You have a lot of discontents.
But since you're so weak,
you can't get
what you want
What did you say?
What did He Na apply to her?
A kind of flower tea.
The white datura tea under the Shorea robusta.
He even got a master to cast a spell of recognizing master.
She will fall in love with the first person she sees at first sight
after she takes off the blindfold.
And...
and...
Didn't you tell me not to let Liu Shao think about you?
I asked them to play hide-and-seek. As long as she sees Aho...
Oh no, Soul-Devouring Spell...
Liu Shao.
[Pearl Pavilion]
Liu Shao,
are you okay?
Oh no.
If she sees me,
will she...?
Lu Li,
do you really think that
I drank that so-called
datura tea?
I was just kidding.
Come out.
Kidding?
That was a show I asked Fattie and He Na to play with me.
You tricked me!
Bad Fattie.
I'll teach him a lesson when I get back.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Why?
Why did you avoid meeting me? Why?
♫This is a spring song♫
I...
♫The peach blossoms fly with the swallow♫
♫Whose lights are light and shine people's way home?♫
Actually, I was not...
I was secretly investigating He Na.
He...
In fact, he's not a little demon underneath
♫The clouds roll the sunset♫
Demon King in White
but Demon King in White.
♫The moon kisses the eyebrows♫
So he is...
♫I am waiting for you to say♫
the one who stole my King Herb.
♫Tonight in this life♫
Yes.
He, the robber, approached you with an ulterior motive.
He pretended to be injured and was picked up by you.
♫Ask the flowing water whether it knows the red leaves♫
I was thinking that he still has King Herb,
♫I miss you so much♫
so I investigated him secretly
to get King Herb back.
♫I still remember the youth♫
♫I laughed and hated getting old♫
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
So,
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
you did it for me
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
♫Send you to the Western State♫
How is it?
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
After you know the truth now,
do you think that
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
your brother Lu Li
is very wise
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
and you admire me so much?
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫
You are not wise at all!
You deliberately avoided meeting me. I was pissed off,
so I beat Fattie up.
Now I want to beat you up too.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I...
I was just afraid that you would reveal it.
Anyway, it's my fault.
It's wrong to hide it from you.
I'm sad, too. I...
What can you do?
I can be sad.
Fine.
But
the Demon King He Na
doesn't look like a bad person.
I need to ask him.
Since he has gotten King Herb,
why did he take the risk to come to Marquis Wuyang's Mansion?
Do you want to
go by yourself? Maybe...
Nothing.
I'll send you out.
[Pearl Pavilion]
Lu Li told me that you were not a little demon.
Yes.
I am the Demon King of the Aquatic Demons, He Na.
Because I am always in white,
I am called Demon King in White.
Did you rob King Herb?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
King Herb has been used by our clan.
I'll remember your kindness.
I will repay you in the future.
No, King...
Is King Herb really gone?
It's true.
I robbed the King Herb
to save people.
Then why did you come back?
I want a drop of blood from you.
My blood?
Oh.
Why don't you ask why?
I believe you have your own reason
for doing this.
I have a lot of blood.
Do you trust me so much?
Of course, I trust you.
Because you are my demon.
What?
I thought Miss Liu Shao
is the destined one to Aquatic Demons.
Unfortunately, I was wrong.
But it's good.
What?
Nothing.
You're not the person I'm looking for.
Oh.
Well,
let's say goodbye.
I'm sorry about King Herb.
I will find a way to make it up to you.
As for why I'm here,
it's not the best time to tell you.
Fine.
Get in!
Do as I say.
Don't waste a moment.
Yes.
Well,
you hide first.
An evil demon has come to the Pearl Pavilion.
All disciples outside,
set an Elixir Sand Formation!
Don't let the demon escape.
How did he know that He Na is hiding here?
I'm the only one here.
There is no demon.
Junior Liu Shao,
I'm really sorry.
I
am just following orders.
You don't look well.
I didn't hear that you were sick.
Tell me.
Where did you hide the demon?
[Pearl Pavilion]
Du,
we didn't find the demon.
I have told you that
there was only me.
Do you believe me now?
If you continue to hide,
I will kill your friend with my sword.
Didn't I ask you to hide in the "Magic Plant Code" and
not to come out?
I'm fine. Hide yourself.
Otherwise, you may be noticed and get stewed.
I said that there was only me.
Du Mingchong,
this is Marquis Wuyang's mansion.
You can't mess around here.
Really?
You collude with the Demon Realm with evil intentions.
Even if I kill you,
Master won't blame me.
Junior Liu Shao,
I'm really sorry.
My friend,
if you don't come out,
Liu Shao will die because of you.
She doesn't know that I'm hiding here
and she is not my friend.
You are an Aquatic Demon.
Demon, die!
Don't hit my fish demon!
Liu Shao!
Fire Whip!
Stop!
Who are you?
I come from Xiyin Mountain.
Xiyin Mountain?
He wears a mask...
Is he the head disciple of the Immortal Master Wanwu,
the most talented lord in Immortal Palace, Lord Wuxiang,
Luo Ge?
It is impossible.
Immortal Palace is condescending.
It doesn't even want to send a fairy here.
How can Lord Wuxiang come in person?
Don't you believe me?
If you are Lord Wuxiang,
please show your power.
He
is the one Xiyin Mountain wants to protect.
It's the first time I've heard that a lord appeared to protect demons.
Why does Xiyin Mountain want to protect a little demon?
When does Xiyin Mountain
need to explain to you?
And Liu Shao
is also someone I value.
No one is allowed to make it difficult for her.
It's him.
Lord is so powerful
that you even know the name of a disciple in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Please show us your power.
You don't deserve it.
Come with me.
[Pearl Pavilion]
He is a liar.
He's not a lord.
We've been tricked.
Chase them!
Go!
Hurry up!
Hurry up.
Help me untie it. Help me untie it.
Bad news, boss.
Slow down!
Boss, bad news!
Why are you in a hurry?
No. Bai Feng and Du Mingchong
went to Pearl Pavilion to catch demons.
I heard that as soon as they got to the Pearl Pavilion,
they smashed everything.
Those with water
were all smashed.
No water was left.
Yes. Even the fish tank was smashed.
He Na's power is weakened without water
and he can't use much magic.
Someone knows his weakness
and wants to kill him.
What should we do?
Let me think.
Little demon,
in order to save you,
I took out my best magic weapons.
How are you going to thank me?
Why do you
have the costume of Lord Wuxiang for no reason?
Do you mean this?
I used these when I cheated...
No, no, no.
I used these when I helped others.
These are not important.
Anyway,
you owe me a favor.
Yes.
Aquatic Demons owe Lu Li and Liu Shao a big favor.
I'll repay you in the future.
No need.
You're welcome.
I can't repay Liu Shao for the time being.
But maybe
I can do you a favor.
Are you under some kind of spell?
Announce the order of Marquis Wuyang.
All disciples
come to the Moon Platform immediately.
I heard that
the Lord who suddenly appeared was fake.
That's why my Lord
comes to the Moon Platform to identify the identity.
Is Lord going to invite the lords in the Immortal Palace?
Even my Lord doesn't know it.
Is that Lord Wuxiang really fake?
How dare he cheated
in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion?
You pretended to be him, right?
Pretending to be Lord... Do you want to die?
Don't worry.
If anything happens, I'll take responsibility.
Marquis Wuyang is here.
I heard that
an envoy of Immortal Palace, Lord Wuxiang, came here today,
but he didn't meet me
Stop pinching.
and left in a hurry.
I would be bruised if you kept pinching.
I don't want to suspect it, but it's too strange.
I must ask the Immortal Palace about it.
Mirror Xuantian
tells the difference.
Marquis Wu Yang,
I've seen the video
you sent through Mirror Xuantian.
I also need to investigate and see
whether the person behind the mask is true or not.
Please check his identity.
Is this the Immortal Wanwu you mentioned?
[Chief of Palace Wuji, Immortal Wanwu]
Something big must have happened.
Immortal Wanwu comes here in person.
Is the fake one among us?
Among us?
Oh no.
This...
This is really over.
Shut up.
He can't be counted as fake.
Your Majesty,
how is it?
I have investigated it.
She isn't the one.
She isn't...
Your Majesty, don't be too sad.
After all, 10 thousand years have passed.
It's not that easy
to find that person.
I thought
even if she's not the person we're looking for,
I must find a chance to repay her.
I took away King Herb she worked hard to find
and put her in danger.
I want a drop of blood from you.
Oh.
Do you trust me so much?
Of course, I trust you.
Because you are my demon.
But after knowing the truth,
she still treated me as her friend
and protected me.
I didn't expect that
I would owe her more.
Your Majesty,
someone named Lu Li is looking for you outside.
Are you under any spell?
Aquatic Demons have long been plagued by spells,
so I know a little about it.
Maybe I can help you.
Can He Na really help me?
Lu Li.
The key to getting rid of the Soul-Devouring Spell
is yourself.
It's because
it doesn't allow me to love.
Yes.
The deeper the love is,
the more pain you are in.
Your fluttering heart,
your love,
and your longing for her
are all burning your life.
You and her...
It should be
love...
I understand now.
Lu Li,
I can only suppress the Soul-Devouring Spell for a while.
If you are badly injured,
or the one who cast the spell triggers the spell and breaks the restriction,
the backlash will lead you to death faster.
All right.
You should be fine for now.
Be careful.
Don't trigger the backlash of the spell.
Don't worry, He Na.
I will find a way to solve the spell
for Liu Shao.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
-Senior, hello. -Senior, hello.
Hello.
Boss,
I think you are Lord Wuxiang
in my mind.
I'll always be your follower.
-Hello, Senior Liu Shao. -Hello, Senior Liu Shao.
Is she the one?
Yes, the one that Lord Wuxiang values.
Why is everyone looking at me?
Am I weird?
Guess it.
-I guess? -Liu Shao.
Lord Liu,
this is specially prepared for you.
What did you call me?
Lord Liu?
Yes, Liu Shao.
You are valued by Lord Wuxiang.
All of us,
everyone,
including Marquis Wuyang,
we have never formally talked to him.
He is
the immortal you've been looking for, right?
Can you tell me
whether Lord Wuxiang is friendly?
He is definitely not as friendly as me.
Friendly?
He is not friendly at all.
Let me tell you.
He
haggles over every ounce
and likes money, right?
Money?
He haggles over every ounce and likes money?
People in the Immortal Palace don't need money.
Right?
I also think that people in the Immortal Palace don't like money.
But Lord Wuxiang
is different from others.
He has a special fetish.
You know, the fetish...
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
I sprained my ankle.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Come out and move it.
Come on.
Get up.
Let's go.
Even a Lord can sprain her ankle when she is sitting.
Don't get carried away.
Do you know you almost revealed it?
Really?
Of course.
Look at how smug you are.
This is not right.
Didn't you say that
you've seen a lot of things?
It is just Lord Luo Ge.
Is it necessary for you to be like this?
Of course not.
I just don't understand
why Immortal Wanwu didn't expose you.
Or
do you know each other?
To be honest,
I'm not sure either.
Could it be that
there is something
between my master and Immortal Wanwu?
Or
Immortal Wanwu thinks that
I look like a lord and have an immortal aura,
and wants to take me as his disciple.
Immortal aura?
You were a liar when I met you.
You're still a liar now.
No immortal aura at all.
Don't I have an Immortal aura?
You don't have an immortal aura at all.
I think I have.
You like it.
Just make do with it.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
We like candies.
Sour and sweet candies.
[Immortal Palace, Palace Chonghua]
Immortal Wanwu.
Lingqi, why are you here?
I heard that Luo Ge appeared in Marquis Wu Yang's mansion.
But he has been in seclusion for more than 20 years.
When did he come out?
He didn't.
[Lord in Immortal Palace, Xie Lingqi]
Then what about the Luo Ge
in the Human Realm?
Luo Ge is born with feelingless talents.
He is the only immortal
who has the chance to become a deity.
His theurgy
is not something ordinary cultivators can reach.
He's in seclusion. That's right.
It's also right that he appeared in the human world.
Everything has its will.
Don't think too much about it.
Just wait for him to come out.
The Immortal Palace
and even the whole Three Realms,
can only rely on Luo Ge in the future.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Things happen
one after another.
I don't have time to find King Herb.
If I still can't find King Herb,
and others know that Marquis Wuyang lost most of his power
because he saved me,
the Human Realm will be in big trouble.
Liu Shao
can't
stay in the mansion anymore.
Since the King Herb Demon King in White owns
has been used,
I need to find a way.
Lu Li,
at this point,
you're still thinking about Liu Shao.
It seems that
you've forgotten what I said.
I dare not.
In your opinion, Ao Hen is a demon.
I think Liu Shao is the demon.
You are obsessed with her.
Not only did you disobey me,
you even disregarded your own life.
Master,
you asked me to protect Liu Shao at that time.
Now she's in danger.
How can I ignore her?
But have you forgotten
the real purpose of protecting her
is to let her help you pull out the Moon Sword
rather than risking your life
to love her.
I have warned you not to fall in love with Liu Shao.
The Soul-Devouring Spell has become this.
Do you want to harm yourself or her?
Master.
Master, don't be angry.
Liu Shao is not sensible.
She doesn't understand the love between boys and girls.
She just...
treated me as a bodyguard she employed.
This is only
my own wishful thinking.
Master,
this has nothing to do with Liu Shao.
Please don't take it out on her.
What wishful thinking!
Kneel!
Master.
Li,
since you don't listen to me,
you'll be punished.
Lu Li,
remember,
I won't allow you to make any mistakes.
The effect of the Soul-Devouring Spell
will only make you suffer more.
The magic of He Na
can't stop Master from triggering the spell.
If you are badly injured,
or the one who cast the spell triggers the spell and breaks the restriction,
the backlash will lead you to death faster.
Lu Li!
Soul-Devouring Spell...
It's Soul-Devouring Spell.
Liu Shao.
Lu Li,
how deep is your love for Liu Shao?
Senior, stop asking.
This has nothing to do with you.
Nothing to do with me?
What do you mean?
Do you know since you gave me malt candy
and said you would protect me that year,
you've been in my heart?
Actually, I've always...
But I'm not in your heart at all.
I...
I've always treated you
as my own sister.
I have never had other thoughts.
If...
If I
did anything that made you misunderstand me,
I apologize.
Apologize?
I've put my heart, soul,
and so many feelings into you.
Can it be ended
by a simple apology?
You are treating me like this
because of Liu Shao?
No matter what you think,
I won't give up.
Also,
no one can interpose between us.